{
    "id": "185aac6616814e05bb7e060ca35e7f95",
    "title": "Hear And Listen To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Did you …………….. the noise?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "35389be656814cb29220cd81063ef805"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………. the news when they came.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearing",
                "listening to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11f7290fdea24bbab4173c5ec95247d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t …………….. you. Can you talk a bit louder?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03c4d18745e94a26a483d2f8b3098dc3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please ……………… me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e277581a6f9a47be8aef8803be4f155f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ………………… about the accident?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4b123b4bc0804b11b5ce340334acab11"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think we can trust him. I have ……………… several strange stories about him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f321e408ac2c441b8ef8c1c878f1e832"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never ………………..  me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listen",
                "listen to",
                "hear"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a1d70419018647db840430d73378402c"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one could …………………. what she said.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "listen",
                "listen to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "688519b602bb49de9590598032294c94"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ……………….. the dogs barking outside.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heard",
                "listened",
                "listened to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "12e0d53b18964b1a853004cc24a7d4ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "When he speaks, everybody ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listens",
                "listens to",
                "hears"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f9261fad9154438a22cc7e75e4aafd3"
        }
    ]
}